this one's super easy take a tautology
jet Bandon good morning good morning
I'm from Kazakhstan despite I look like
yes previous Mojtaba weekly yeah it's my
pleasure
okay these it means that in fact it
means Oh mani padmi who don't use these
teaching as fashion yes
don't make yourself famous or something
like that but really understand it and I
use it to upgrade it okay yes so this is
the meaning of these cool and this
mantra means that I want to act like a
Buddha I want to talk like a Buddha I
want to think like a Buddha and there is
nothing in my teachers that not comes
from me and my teacher is like a diamond
in a lot of super perfect
oh jesus oh jesus saw paddy seditious or
$100 if I'm raising cannot huh oh okay
you get from her okay
she's happy don't forget Valentina
otherwise she will keep it friend AHA
what Suzy follicle tada tada
that is take a mean tuna
viola this is some serious you don't
have a choice in artesian city the holy
sister
Oh Moneypenny on the institution we as
young photo a young seen way young you
and Zoe a whole large sir
partisans imagine how the difference
pulling through what the tones that
young Leia Han Jahn - yeah yeah I think
we should give sternly hand for
translation without me I can say just a
little tiny
[Applause]